There is nothing wrong,
nor will there ever be wrong,
with any Sabre printers.
Case cIosed.
(PHONE RlNGlNG)
Michael Scott,
as seen on TV.
MAN ON PHONE: I saw you
on the news and I want to
pinch your tiny wiener.
(MOUTHS) Oh, my God.
It's Packer.
Oh ! Pac-Man,
l thought you were a girl.
Apparently,
there are allegations
that Sabre printers
can cause a fire.
So, they asked me to give
a statement to the press.
So, l do it.
lt's on TV last night,
and it's in the paper today,
and it's online.
And then l call Froggy 98.7,
their request line.
l talked to the host
about it on the air.
lt's like,
"Come on, people, enough."
Everybody,
we are at DEFCON 5.
l am officially
the second most watched
clip of the day
on the WBRE news site.
What's number one?
Oh? That teacher who
was wrongfully accused
of being a pedophile.
Now, we cannot let
the pedophile win again.
l would like you all
to go to the Web site
and watch my clip 1 1 times.
So, instead of working,
you want. . .
Yes.
Okay.
MlCHAEL: Come on.
Get it up.
That's what. . .
Let's do it.
Oh ! Did you
see this report
that the zoo
got a baby otter?
lt's on the same site.
(CHUCKLES) Aw!
lt's kissing its mommy.
MlCHAEL: Please.
Michael, you have to
see this.
This is, like,
the cutest thing ever.
(EMPLOYEES LAUGHlNG)
Really? A baby otter?
Okay, count me in
as "Who cares?"
lt's not even
that interesting,
the baby otter.
lt can't even stand up.
lt's trying to stand up.
There he goes.
(DOG BARKlNG)
Howdy.
l hope l'm not
interrupting anything.
Jo, we were
not expecting you.
But you all no doubt
know why l'm here.
No.
Turns out our
printers are famous.
They're all over
the news.
lt's an
interesting story.
Cheap, foreign printers
attacking
innocent Americans.
Well, actually
the real story
isn't quite as racy.
But
let's give it a go.
Jo, l think that
l know what happened.
l'm not sure you do,
teddy bear.
Well, now l think
l might not.
Not long ago,
we discovered a defect
in one of our printers.
So, we got
a software patch,
fixed it right up.
Just like that.
l don't know
how it works.
Just as we
were about to
send out a letter to
our affected customers,
giving them free toner,
and we keep them happy.
But somebody here,
they liked that
first story better.
The one where
we lose half our clients
(SHOUTlNG)
for no damn good reason !
Whoever it was who
talked to the press,
just come forward, please.
MlCHAEL: Jo,
l can assure you it was
no one in this office.
Can you, now?
Absolutely.
Anyone who
talked to the press,
please raise your hand.
Put your hand up,
Norma Rae.
lf you say anything,
so help me God,
l'll break off
the temples of
your glasses
and stick them in
your eye sockets.
ANDY: So unfair.
Even if l thought
that our printers
killed baby seals,
l would not be
a whistleblower.
The Bernards,
for generations,
have silenced whistleblowers.
lt's how
we made all our money.
Woody Guthrie
wrote a song about us.
OId Mister Bernard
Who have you silenced today?
lt's a little form.
Says, "l did not do it."
There is no reason
for anyone here
to sign this
because l know
everything there is to know
about these people.
l know when
their birthdays are,
l know what their
favorite kind of cake is,
l know what color
streamers they like.
All that's just
birthday information,
Michael.
Yes, yes, but it
shows a bigger picture.
Why don't you
come with me?
We'll start out
with the honcho,
what d'you say?
Okay.
When Mama was working
as a prison guard,
and something went missing,
she'd ask one question,
"What do we do
when we find
the guilty party?"
And if they said,
"Come down on them
"with that swift hammer
of justice," innocent.
A clear conscience
don't need no mercy.
But if they said,
"Officer Bessie, well,
they may have had a reason."
Blah, blah, blah, blah. . .
Well, nine times out of 1 0,
that's the anus they checked.
So, say we catch
this whistleblower.
What do you think
l should do with them?
We should give them
a one-way ticket
to Montego Bay.
Where they keep
all the al-Qaeda.
Uh, that's
Guantanamo Bay.
Yes.
You put them in jail
for a long time,
you put them in jail
for as long as you can.
Well, l guess we're
all right, Michael.
l want these people
to really pay.
l want them to suffer.
l'd prefer it
if they died.
Because it's not right.
Yeah.
Okay.
Hey, Dwight.
Hey, lT guy.
You mind if l get in
there for a second?
Oh, sure thing,
go ahead.
Just. . . (GROANlNG)
Dwight, what the hell?
Apache persuasion hold,
that's the hell.
What are you doing
to my computer?
The lawyers are searching
our hard drives for
information on the leak.
Thanks a lot, Big Brother.
You're with Big Brother?
Okay, go ahead.
l got nothing to hide.
Wait, are they searching
all our computers?
Yeah.
NlCK: l already
got to yours, Kev.
No, that's cool.
Sometimes l run.
l'm a runner.
Everybody knows
it was Andy,
and it is not fair for
us all to take the fall
for his big, stupid mouth.
Ridiculous, Angela.
And like l'm going to
believe one of
his spurned lovers.
Look, he's been complaining
about this for a while.
lt's not crazy.
(PHYLLlS SCOFFS)
Okay, Dwight.
Hold that thought.
l don't want to
waste your time
and l wouldn't
dare waste mine.
l didn't do it.
Now, l don't know
exactly who did it,
but l have a list
right here.
You should fire
the following people.
Well, l'm inclined
to believe you.
Why would l disparage
a company that has
made me rich beyond
my wildest dreams?
Yeah, l noticed
you've had a great year.
Good boy.
(LAUGHlNG)
You turning that money
into more money?
Are you referring
to alchemy?
l don't like to tell a man
what to do with his money,
but if you ain't
investing in property,
then you're
dumber than a dummy.
l'm not dumb, l'm smart.
Well, buy property.
That's my advice.
MlCHAEL: ls there
something that you would
like to say to me?
About talking
to the press?
Uh, l do. . . No. . .
l didn't do that. Okay?
Didn't do it.
l don't believe you.
l swear on
the graves of my parents
who aren't even dead yet.
That's a little much.
All right, all right.
l don't care.
That's how much, l swear.
Okay, l believe you.
l believe you.
How come no one's
giving Darryl any crap?
He was more bothered
about it than me.
Did you tell anyone
outside of this office
that the printers
were catching on fire?
Yeah, l did.
(SlGHS)
l was talking to
this girl at a bar.
Oh, no, no, no.
l think she could
sense my sadness.
And l found out
too late that she was
a copyeditor at the Trib.
Oh, my God.
Was she cute?
No.
Oh, God, Darryl.
l basically swore up
and down that none
of my employees did it.
And then l find out
that one of
my best ones did.
And now he's probably
going to get fired for it.
And if that is
not poetic justice,
l don't know what is.
Sounds like you were
as blind-sided
by this as l was.
Yes.
And we didn't find anything
on your computer.
Good.
Except this.
Wow. This is just
a mystery novel that
l've been working on.
l know what it is.
l skimmed the first chapter.
l'm just curious,
why would a man
who hates people
want to have
a relationship with a maid?
l don't know. . .
The way l look at it,
there's only one
of two reasons.
He knows a secret
about her that she
doesn't know herself.
Or he wants to
use her services
to mop up after a murder.
(EXCLAlMS)
Yes.
Write your own damn novel.
lt was me.
What was you?
You were the leak?
Okay,
l'm talking to this
woman at day care,
she's telling me all
about her amazing trip
to Vietnam. l have nothing.
l tell her our printers
catch on fire spontaneously.
Why'd you do that?
Her husband's
a reporter.
Yeah.
So, now everyone hates Andy,
and it's this whole mess,
and l don't know
what to do.
Okay, just relax.
Just need to relax.
l could tell Jo,
or l could tell Michael.
This is a very good idea.
This is good.
Let's get all
the bad ideas out now.
Flush them out.
(WHlSPERS) You leaked it?
l don't know what to do.
Do l go tell Jo or. . .
l don't want everyone
to keep blaming
the wrong person.
l don't know what
the best plan is, Pam.
Oh, God.
My mind is going
a mile an hour.
That fast?
(GROANS)
Two whistleblowers. Two.
l always thought
Darryl and Pam
might get me fired
for something l said.
Yeah?
l weirdly know exactly
what you're saying to me.
So, l'll see you
in Meredith's van
in five minutes.
Okay, you didn't need
to actually say that.
l have never seen
so many parking tickets.
All right,
this is just messed up.
No, you know
what's messed up?
This situation
all up in here
is what's messed up.
We need to brainstorm,
we need to get out of this.
Brain-hurricane, come on.
Think. What have we got?
Um. . .
Hey, guys,
sorry l'm late.
We're not going
for yogurt.
lt's okay, she's cool.
She also whistle-blew.
Guys, l couldn't help it.
lt is so boring
where we work.
l mean, it's as interesting
as a morgue.
lt might be less interesting
than a morgue.
Hey, hey, it's as
interesting as a morgue.
Of course l'm the leak.
l think l tweeted it.
l can't control
what l say to people.
l spend
the whole day talking.
l mean, l video chat,
l skype, l text,
l tweet, l phone, l woof.
Woof is a site that
l'm launching to be
the last word in
social networking.
For just $1 2.99 a month,
Woof links up
all your
communication portals,
so you are
always within reach.
lt's part of the dog pack,
as l call it.
But look, why tell you,
when l can show you?
l just sent myself a woof.
(DOG BARKlNG)
(ALL MACHlNES BEEPlNG)
ERlN ON lNTERCOM:
Ryan, you have a woof
on Iine one.
Thank you, Erin.
Woof!
Okay, here's what we do.
l say we just smash
all the computers.
We destroy the evidence.
No evidence, no case.
Wouldn't we get fired
for smashing
all the computers?
No, okay,
not all the computers.
Just our computers.
That idea sucks.
PAM: l don't think
that's a good idea.
MlCHAEL: Just don't say no.
Mike, you know
you don't have to
turn us all in.
All you need is
one scapegoat.
Uh, if you turn me in,
l'm turning in Darryl.
That's just what we need,
another black man
in prison, you know?
Nobody's going
to prison. Okay?
All right, Michael,
you need to convince
Jo to go easy on us.
And then we'll
all confess once we know
our jobs are safe.
Okay, you can
count on me.
Let me give you
a hand.
Ready?
On three.
(CELL PHONE RlNGlNG)
Oh, shoot. Got it?
Got it.
Dwight Schrute.
REALTOR: The property
you're looking at
is in great shape.
By the way,
it has a very
spacious basement office.
Basement office?
You mean like a lair?
Hey, Jo.
Michael.
l was thinking about
our little leak problem.
l was up all lunch
thinking about
what we should do
to this individual.
You know what l
think we should do?
We make them
come to work.
And we work them,
and we make them sit
next to all the people
they screwed over.
And we pay them,
but we make them
feel like they did
something really wrong.
The one question
l have is, "Do we give them
a Christmas bonus?"
l say yes, it's Christmas,
but right after,
they're back into
the thick of it.
Michael Scott.
What do you know?
What?
lt doesn't matter
what l know.
lf it doesn't matter,
then tell me.
Why?
Because l wanna deal with it
the way l deal with it.
Well, deal with this.
Empathize with me
for a moment.
l came up here
with a big problem,
and now,
l've got a branch manager
who's giving me
the silent treatment.
Speak to me.
Speak.
(BARKS)
Come with me.
What?
Are you leaving? Oh, my.
Should l continue
with the investigation?
Are you gonna kill me?
(JO LAUGHlNG)
REALTOR: Ijust need you
to come by later
and sign a few forms.
Okay.
What time
works for you?
Mr. Schrute? What time works?
Cancel it.
l want you to make an offer
at 1 725 Slough Avenue.
Make them an offer
they can't refuse.
No, on second thought,
lowball them.
Don't call me
till you have it.
But...
MlCHAEL: Are we going
someplace far away?
l know you said
no questions,
but l have an early dinner
that l need to get to.
With the chief of police.
l'm very relieved
to learn it wasn't you.
All right.
Stan, you're up.
lt wasn't me.
What a rich timbre
your voice has.
Okay, l am prepared
to conclude
the investigation.
ANDY: And?
You did it.
What? Based on what?
Just all the evidence.
And it really seems
like it was you.
Can we all agree to say
that it was Andy for now
and sit with it,
see how it feels?
All right,
sounds good.
Okay.
Guys, l think that
seems a little unfair.
l mean, l feel like
we don't definitely
know it was Andy.
Yeah, you know?
l mean, for all we know,
it could have been Jim.
Really?
Michael.
l have rights.
Let's just talk.
l am not going to
tell you anything.
Honey, you don't seem
like your normal self.
Well, l'm going through
a little bit of
a rough patch.
Mama Jo knew
there was something up.
The whole year, actually.
My favorite restaurant
closed down.
Oh.
l hate that.
And my new favorite
restaurant sucks.
l bought a video camera
last year
and l was looking
at the tapes,
and there were only,
like, 1 2 minutes that
l felt was worth taping.
The whole year.
And most of that
was just birds in
my condo complex.
What is that?
And l miss Holly.
Who's Holly?
Holly Flax.
From the Nashua branch.
Best HR rep
that Dunder Mifflin
has ever seen.
lt has not been
a blockbuster year
for me financially.
My Blockbuster
stock is down.
l think that
the real question is,
"Who is the whistleblower?"
Just. . .
l may have heard
from an old client
and l may have immediately
started spreading
the news to other clients
and potential clients, yeah.
But l'm not here
to talk about that.
l'm here to talk
about Suck lt. Suck lt. . .
Gabe, l told you all
about the printers.
JlM: l mean,
it could be you, Gabe.
Yes, it's totally obvious.
l mean,
that's the point.
l think we all can agree
it's either Gabe or Angela.
lt's Angela.
Get her, boys.
Hey, guys.
Sorry to interrupt.
l just wanted to say
goodbye to everyone.
Through Teach For America,
l'm going to go
down to Detroit
and teach inner-city kids
about computers.
Not now.
NlCK: Yeah, it's just
that my friends
are in the car waiting,
so l thought l'd. . .
(WHlSPERlNG) Phyllis, what's
this guy's name again?
l don't know.
ls it Shadow or Garth?
lt's something weird, l. . .
My name is Nick.
Okay, well, "Nick,"
we're in a meeting.
Okay, look, l get it, people.
l'm the lame lT guy
and everybody hates me.
Hey, listen, man,
you can't take it
personally.
You call me "man"?
l just said my name,
just now. Did you
forget it already?
No,
sport.
You guys have 1 5 parties
a week. You can't
learn my name?
Hey, hey, hey, lT guy.
Here's the story, champ.
None of us have spent
a lot of time getting
to know you, okay?
We liked the last guy, Sadiq,
because he kept to himself.
And we also thought
he might have
been a terrorist.
You know what?
l'm going to leave you
with one other thought.
lnner-city kids use
computers for two things,
games and porn.
So, good luck
wasting your life, Lurch.
Thank you so much for that.
l saw all of
your hard drives.
And guess what?
You're not a photographer.
And you definitely
can't fit into a size two.
Darryl, man,
you're on Facebook.
Why have you
been telling people
you're not on Facebook?
People want to be
your friend, man.
KELLY: Hey.
All right?
And you. . . This guy.
You're the one
who told the press.
You wrote
an e-mail to the editor.
l saw it and l also
saw a Quicktime movie
of your little
printer fire test
on your hard drive.
This guy's the snitch,
he's the snitch. So,
that's it. Check it out.
We're going to
believe that guy?
When l was growing up,
there was nothing better
than being a big old
business tycoon.
And l thought l'd
break that glass ceiling
and be a hero
to all those
little girls out there.
And they'd make
a Barbie out of me.
(CHUCKLES CASUALLY)
l hate that
l sell cheap printers.
l do.
But if l have to
go out there
in front of the press
and make one of them
public apology recalls,
l mean, that's all l'll
ever be remembered for.
Nobody will want to
play with my Barbie.
(CLlCKS TONGUE)
Well, you know,
l would be willing,
under the right
circumstances,
to do that for you.
Oh, honey, surely
you don't want that.
(CLlCKS TONGUE)
l surely do,
and don't call me honey.
(BOTH LAUGHlNG)
Airplane II.
l'm about to buy
this building, you know?
You don't say.
l own a one-eighth share
in a rental property
down in Pittston.
Well, l'm one-eighths
proud of you.
Enjoy that chair for now.
'Cause pretty soon you
will be on your feet.
Like Buckingham Palace.
Hey, Phyllis,
have you seen my bag?
You deserve it.
ANDY: Look, l didn't want
houses and schooIs
to burn down
and chiIdren to die.
Does that make me a hero?
KEVlN: No, it does not.
Well, it doesn't make me
the worst guy in the world,
either.
ANGELA: lt does!
Andy?
Hey.
l wanted to say that
l think it was very brave
of you to go to the press.
Thanks.
Yeah, you know.
Just seemed like
the right thing to do.
Yeah.
"We at Sabre have
betrayed the trust
"that we have built
with our customers.
"We regret our slow response
and our lapse in
candor and judgment.
"At this time,
we are issuing a full recall
of all Sabre GH400 printers.
"We will not rest
until this problem
is solved.
"There will be no questions."
Are there any questions?
Hey, l appreciate you
reading that statement.
You looked pretty up there.
That was fun.
l hope your rough patch
ends soon.
Thanks. Today helped.
Well, give a shout
if l can brighten your life.
Okay. Hey, you could
transfer Holly back
from Nashua.
Let me see what l can do.